Register of the Poland. Ministerstwo Spraw Zagranicznych Records, 1919-1947.
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1940-1943, (162 prints / 13 envelopes (Box 59003 - Photo file)
  - 3 photos depicting railroad warehouses of Commission for Polish Relief in Geneva, Switzerland with boxes and cardboard drums destined for deliveries to Poland., 1942 (Folder L)
  - 1 photo depicting 94 volumes of accounting records submitted with the annual report of the Financial Adviser to the Polish Embassy in the Soviet Union., January 1, 1943 (Folder M)